Is it really possible to get a full body workout
with one kettlebell in 15 minutes?
Of course. Let me show you.
I call this complex fives.
We're doing five different exercises,
five reps apiece. We're gonna start with these close grip push UPS.
I want you to take these slow and controlled
so that we get time under tension.
We can focus on the form, keeping the core tight,
activating the chest and triceps.
We're going to take this right into the deadlift with a high pull.
Take your time with these reps
so you don't get too much momentum from the legs.
So we can still get proper,
proper activation of your upper body.
From these.
We'll go straight into five kettlebell swings.
As always focusing on the hip hinge,
finding that tension through the glutes and the hamstrings.
We're gonna take this right into five goblet squats,
dropping down below 90 degrees and driving the ground away from you.
And last but not least, we got five push press.
Repeat that complex as many times as you can in 15 minutes,
and you got yourself a perfectly adequate full body workout.
If you like efficient and effective workouts using minimal equipment,
give me a follow. We'll see you next time.